Apple number 43 I believe is adopt a
stranger for the holidays this last
Thanksgiving I hadn't planned a lot just
me my daughter
Thanksgivings on a super important
holiday and so I didn't have anything
planned and I was lonely and I was
feeling like a crappy mother from having
been planned and someone posted online
that they had an open space at their
Thanksgiving dinner for a single mom and
a child that was like sure I'll do it
and it's amazing I mean I love her and
her family and her husband her son in
their family three and we've made
friends and it's I mean it was
Thanksgiving this last year so and then
she came to my house for Christmas when
I had my mom and dad here and I realized
they're not all gonna go that well but I
think no matter what your traditions are
especially when you're away from home
and not able to celebrate them the same
way being able to offer a space to
someone else we're being able to accept
one of those spaces would be amazing and
so Appl number 43 is adopted strange for
the holiday app